Okay, it is um project time. So, uh
don't forget your name and description
at the top.
Um in this uh homework, we're going to
be a pizza shop. So, I want you to make
an array which has objects inside of it
that are storing the name, price, and
whether or not the pizza is vegetarian.
Um I've given dummy data right below
that you can see. I want you to add um a
new pizza to the array programmatically.
I want you to use the spread operator um
strategically to create a new array that
also has a cow zone. Um I want you to
map the new array to just the pizza
names and print the results. I want you
to filter to only vegetarian pizzas. I
want you to reduce to figure out how
much it would cost you to buy one of
each type of pizza. I want you to find
to sort by price. Then I want you to
dstructure the very first object in that
sorted array to get the name and price.
Then I want you to write a function that
will allow someone to search through
your array um by name and find an object
in it. And then finally, I want you to
create an array where each element is
another array where it has the pizza
name and price. And I want you to print
that array. Good luck.